Good afternoon, sir.
Oh, my God.
Today is your seventh.
So today I'm going to
I'd like to answer a hundred questions.
I'll do my best.
I won't. That's not what I'm talking about.
This is Iwate Prefecture's "Sasakukura Hinano." Our member color is orange.
Hm...
My nickname is Hinamon-chan.
It's May 6th, 2004
The world is bad.
I'm going about my daily life as usual, or I'll be thankful for it.
Liquid is...
Tare...
Peaches and tsukune.
Oh, sauce...
Hmm? Oh, the mandarin orange mark? I used to be kind of a huge tiger, but now I'm okay with it. Now I know they're full of nutrients.
Favorite hairstyle? Twin-tail or twin style.
I wear my hair in a bob.
Do you like spicy food? As long as it's spicy.
What color would you dye your hair?
Pink because that's what people say when they ask me what color looks good on me.
Do you believe in ghosts?
I think there are, but I don't see any.
What is your personal favorite sound of food?
The sound of rice.
Rustling.
Meat.
The sound of rice.
Saya ko
ah, cotton, ah, kinu, kinu, kinu da, kinu
I've been to ramen, kaidama, nampa-ken, even
I want to go to Sanmu
Seven o'clock in the satellite
Wow, contacts, I definitely can't buy them if I forget, not reallyWow, contacts, I definitely can't buy them if I forget, not really.
Band salad kid.
Maybe a bass player.
Cool, I'm going to peel and eat a baked potato.
I recently had a dream that my bangs were all stuck together.
My favorite season is autumn, but in that order... autumn, winter, spring and summer.
Rice is bread is rice?
What flavor of ramen do you prefer? Pork bone broth.
Free transportation for life is everywhere.
I don't know.
Sushi is salmon
Salmon
Oh, but I kind of like Thai lately
Oh, go!
If you can change your name...
Um, Kiairi Tsukishita
If you can change the name of the group
I'd like a group with English name.
What is your favorite word?
Be kind to yourself and to others.
Where can we travel in Japan?
Right now, I'm going to Hakone Onsen.
I would like to go to Korea if I can travel abroad.
Korean food
What do you do on your day off?
Sleeping or playing games since I've been playing a lot of games lately.
But mostly sleeping.
How many meals a day?
A day...hmmm...sometimes one meal, sometimes two.
My favorite animals are bears and cats.
Favorite lyrics and song...
It's the same person, isn't it?
Lately, I've been into Aiko's music.
My favorite song is...
Well, I don't know... I like them all...
I like all of them, but I think it's the song "Happiness".
or "Hanabi, Hanabi" (Fireworks)Fireworks. Fireworks.
Favorite English word?
Let's see...
TV blues.
Do you have a driver's license? I don't have a license. I want to get one.
How fast are you in 500 meters?
Oh, 50 meters.
Fifty meters.
He shook his head sideways.
50m is the kinkiest thing I can remember,
Really,
Seven seconds? Not that fast, maybe 8.2?
7.50, maybe even 7.50.
What is your favorite subject?
Haiku?
Home economics?
Shyness?
I was shy at first.
My boom is cooking.
If you were to compare yourself with one Kanji character, what would it be?
If you were to compare yourself with one kanji character, what would it be?
What would it be?
Love of cuteness
The highest whistle I can give out
I can't produce
Low voice
What's a decibel? That's a decibel.
Any quirks?
I don't know.
Habits you don't even know you have.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
Habit?
I can sleep anywhere.
My favorite Twoxxon song.
Yes, I do.
Now...Now...
now
what is it?
I don't know.
But...
Clothes, voice...
What I'm thinking about during the show...
Let's see...
I'm thinking...
When I see a guest with a name board or some other goodies.
I imagine what it will be like when they are at home.
What was your favorite part of the show? Oh, I don't know.
But when we were on tour, it was the bubble poppies.
There's a part on the tour where they stretch out the "we are the power" part of the bubble poppies, and...
I enjoyed it when Kaya arranged it a little bit and stretched it out a little bit.
Favorite ingredient in a pot?
I wonder.
Taro? Yam?
Yams?
Favorite oden ingredient?
My favorite oden ingredient is
Daikon radish
Who do you admire?
I'd love to have kashigaki.
If you could take one thing with you to a deserted island...
Doraemon
If you were going to a deserted island, who would you take with you?
Let's see...
Hikaru?
Not because I think he'd be useful, but because...
I want to die with a happy heart.
Who would you switch with?
Oh, I don't know.
Hmmm...
Who?
I'd like to be me.
If I were a man, I wouldn't want to be in a relationship.If I were a man, I'd be in trouble for dating.
Ahh.
I wonder who he is.
What's that?
If you were a man, right?
But I think it's Hikaruun.
He's...
The more you know about him, the deeper you get.
What's the sport you'd like to play?
What would it be?
I can't swim and play ball games that don't use a racket, like basketball and volleyball, so if I can do them, I'd like to try them.
I want to be the best dancer in the world.
I want to be the best singer in the world.
Will I be the best singer in the world?
How tall will I be?
I will never get fat in my life.
Oh, I'm not sure. I will never get fat.
I want to eat. A lot.
A word to the grinners.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
What song do you recommend?
Oh, recommended songs?
Hmmm...
I don't know. I think it's a good song.
It's...
Seishun Shugaku Ryoko (Youth School Trip)
I wonder?
It's full of Tohoku's style.
What time do you get up?
Lately...
I go to bed around 3:00.
On my days off.
I'll go for a juice or something.
Do you wear clothes or pajamas to bed?
Pajamas, definitely.
Would you live in the country?Would you like to live in the country?
Hmmm...
People.
I don't mind being around people.
I'd live in the city.
If you could change your member color, what would it be?
Wow, I don't know.
If I had to change...
Hmmm...
Something corn, corn or black.
Most expensive purchase you've ever made.
Most expensive purchase you ever made?
Yes, it is.
It's something I bought myself.
I don't know.
Huh?
A hair iron?
Oh, maybe a bag? Maybe a bag. A bag.
Scariest experience?
My worst fear?
That, too.
Well, after I said good night to my mom.
I was playing a game, and then my mom came in to take a peek.
I thought she was gone, so I started to play,
There she was.
You know, that onigiri you like.
Kelp or salmon roe.
What would you like to do in the arts?
Ah.
what's that?
I don't know.
A job in the arts.
Voice actor.
Like voice actors.
Take the seeds of the watermelon first.
Where you can get it, you take it first.Where I can get it, I take it first.
I ate watermelon when I was little, which I never thought possible before.
It is unthinkable now.
I wonder what it is.
There was something. I wonder what it was.
That's exactly what I noticed recently,
Rest,
You know, a fairy tale.
I used to think it was a profession.
I was really, really surprised.
Hikaru told me about it during this tour,
I was really shocked.
How many have you seen now? Oh, I haven't seen it.
I thought it was 63 or something.
Wrong.
What were you like when you were little?
Ex-kid.
Naughty.
Water or tea? Tea drinker?
Tea.
I'm a tea drinker.
How did you feel when you played your own music?
Well, I don't know.
I like vocaloids.
I don't know, it's kind of like a Vocaloid song.
Songs...
There are not so many mysterious songs like that.
Songs like that...
Something a little
Something deep.
Karaoke...
That's a problem.
I don't know, but that's exactly what it is.
Aiko sings a lot.
Beetle.
The moment when you celebrate New Year's Eve?New Year's Eve moment?
Let's jump!
The moment to celebrate New Year's Eve?
I'll have some soba or something.
Time for a photo op?
Yes, I do.
What are you doing on the road?
I'm either sleeping, or I'm turning on a switch.
Talking.
When we watch a movie, I always ask for something.
A drink, of course.
And popcorn.
Drinks.
But sometimes I'll have a hot dog or a churro.
They are delicious, aren't they?
I was in the art club.
Why art club?
I had to be in a club at my school at that time,
I really wanted to go home.
I really wanted to join the tennis club,
I really wanted to join the tennis club, but Mommy told me I couldn't join the tennis club because it was too hot,
I thought I wanted to join the club, but I had to join,
I asked the teacher what kind of club would be easiest for me,
I asked the teacher what kind of club would be easiest for me, and she said art club, so I decided to join it.
I joined the art club and had fun.
What is a difficult song by TALK?
What is it?
I don't know.
I think there was something.
I wonder.
But then again, I don't know.
I Decided
I sing for a long time
I tend to sing for a long time
That's the difficult part.
How did you get into show business?How did you get into show business?
I always wanted to work in the entertainment industry, or rather, in public.
How did you get into this company?
I was scouted by a scout.
Do you believe in fate?
I might believe in fate.
Favorite YouTuber?
I don't know.
Sushi Ramen Rickku.
He's so funny.
He and his dog
The dialogue between him and his dog is funny.
What were you addicted to when you were little?
When I was little, I was addicted to...
That one.
I don't know.
I tried dancing.
It was popular in the past.
Vocaloids...
I don't know...
Anime, etc.
and free copying them.
I danced and sang.
I guess my point is...
When I sing...
I like to sing and I enjoy it.
When she talks...
And when he talks...
And...
And when you try to get along with me.
And I'm cute.
What are your hobbies?
Hobbies?
Hobbies?I wonder what his hobbies are.
Singing, I guess.
Listening to music.
I listen to music all the time.
Do you prefer to confess or wait?
I don't know.
I don't really like waiting.
I'm not good at waiting.
I'm a person who takes action immediately.
No matter what it is.
I'm the type of person who takes action right away, even when I'm traveling.
I think I'm a do-er.
I'm good at swimming.
I can't swim! I can't swim! I really can't swim!
I used to have something.
Dolphin gummies.
Jellyfish gummies, jellyfish gummies...
There were jellyfish gummies.
They were like a scene, the worst swimmers.
Like, I can't even doggy paddle.
I don't want to brag about it, but...
You want to be a part of a living army?
Wow, there's a lot of places.
Let's see...
I want to go to that! I want to go glamping! I want to go camping and barbecue with everyone! It'll be fun!
I'm a Western foodie! I'm a Western foodie!
I like Italian food.
I can only eat plain ginger.
But if you're smart, you can have all kinds.
How about a bento box? Is that cheating?
It's okay. I'd like to go to a live concert.
I don't know.
Where would you like to play?
Music hall? Open-air music hall? Is there a place like that? I'd like to do it there.
When you say you're an animal...When I say I am to an animal.
A miniature cat or dog
I would consider each member as an animal. Each and every member! Oh, my God.
I'll go in order of age.
Hikaru is a bunny
Rine is a cat?
She's a Russian blue.
And Yuna... what's Yuna...
But...
Cute monkey.
Just a little cute when I say monkey.
Monkey because of the way he laughs like this.
The young dog is Kabibara.
This is your favorite animal?
But it's kind of woofing.
The pearl...
Is it a thingy?
It's like a panda.
She's cute no matter what she does.
What about Karen?
Is there an animal that's doing well?
Animals that work hard.
Horses, for example. Like horse racing.
They don't look like horses, but they are like horses.
It's not really a bad word for it.
I don't know. Let's say it's cute. A cat.
A nickel cat.
Mew, because I said so earlier.
Miu Miu is really a baby cat.
I think Kaya-san is like a golden retriever.
Kaya-san is like a golden retriever.
In a word, what is your selling point?
What is it?
Tork is something,
Born naturally,
Like children.
I don't know,Something,
Oh, I guess it's like this.
We're really good friends,
I think Sato is wonderful,
And then there's the other thing,
I mean, there are so many different kinds of music and stuff,
It's fun! We are very similar.
Singer you would like to play with?
Singers?
A band? I don't know what it is, but a band?
Part-time job?
I would like to work in customer service or at a cash register.
What is your favorite candy?
Sweets or...
Fried potato
What is your favorite part?
You have to be creative.
You try to be creative
You try to share your thoughts with us.
Thank you for that.
What do you want us to fix?
What do you want me to fix? I don't know.
What do you want me to fix?
I don't think so.
No, not really.
If I did, I'd tell you directly.
A word of love to you all.
Thank you for everything.
Keep up the good work.
What is your ultimate goal as Mr. Tork?
My ultimate goal as Mr. Tork is...
I don't know...
To be big.
Become famous
I want to be someone
know meI want to be someone who knows
To finally meet a member from far away.
Wow, that makes me cry.
I don't know what I'd do if you hadn't all said something that made me cry.
This is gonna sting just a little bit.
What about seeing them?
Because I got to meet you all.
I have no regrets about the past seven years.
Thank you. Always. Please keep in touch with me.
Even if I become a grandmother, please be good friends with me. Please do.
Oh, even in the next life.
Um, please.
I finished 100 questions.
I wonder. Surprisingly, I'm not the one who answered them all by now.
I thought I could answer quite a few,
I guess that's how you got to know me.
I would love to have another hundred outings in the future,
So, thank you for watching the video.
If you haven't seen any of the other members, please do.
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating.
Bye bye!